https://tecla.com/privacy-policy/

Tecla EditionsAuthors/ComposersAguado, DionisioCarcassi, MatteoGiuliani, MauroSor, FernandoMore composers A-ZCerruti, WenceslasBeethoven – The 32 Piano Sonatas in very high quality facsimile reprints of all 32 of the first editions.Bent , James TheodoreBosch, JaimeColla, VincenzoComoglio, Jean (Giovanni)Costa, OnoratoCoste, NapoléonCottin , AlfredCutting, FrancisDegen, SøffrenDiabelli , AntonDowland, JohnDojcinovic, UrosFerandiere, FernandoFerrari, G.G.Fossa, François deGatayesGuerau, FranciscoHolborne, AntonyHolst, Matthias vonJeffery, BrianKiselev, OlegLute music arranged for guitarMangado, Josep MariaManjón , Antonio JimenezMatiegkaFrancesco MolinoMolino , ValentinoMoretti, FedericoMoretti , LuigiNava , AntonioPadovec, IvanPolletPonce, Manuel M.Pilkington, FrancisRung, HenrikSalvo, Francesco deSchubertShopAll Books and Music ScoresMost Popular ProductsAssociated Board (ABRSM)Music for voice and guitarGuitar SolosGuitar DuetsCDsInfoOrdering and shippingAbout TeclaMy Account/LoginContact TeclaReviewsTradePoliciesPrivacy PolicyReturns PolicyShipping PolicySecurity PolicyCookie PolicyTerms and ConditionsDigital Downloads (PDF)
MenuAuthors/ComposersAguado, DionisioCarcassi, MatteoGiuliani, MauroSor, FernandoMore composers A-ZCerruti, WenceslasBeethoven – The 32 Piano Sonatas in very high quality facsimile reprints of all 32 of the first editions.Bent , James TheodoreBosch, JaimeColla, VincenzoComoglio, Jean (Giovanni)Costa, OnoratoCoste, NapoléonCottin , AlfredCutting, FrancisDegen, SøffrenDiabelli , AntonDowland, JohnDojcinovic, UrosFerandiere, FernandoFerrari, G.G.Fossa, François deGatayesGuerau, FranciscoHolborne, AntonyHolst, Matthias vonJeffery, BrianKiselev, OlegLute music arranged for guitarMangado, Josep MariaManjón , Antonio JimenezMatiegkaFrancesco MolinoMolino , ValentinoMoretti, FedericoMoretti , LuigiNava , AntonioPadovec, IvanPolletPonce, Manuel M.Pilkington, FrancisRung, HenrikSalvo, Francesco deSchubertShopAll Books and Music ScoresMost Popular ProductsAssociated Board (ABRSM)Music for voice and guitarGuitar SolosGuitar DuetsCDsInfoOrdering and shippingAbout TeclaMy Account/LoginContact TeclaReviewsTradePoliciesPrivacy PolicyReturns PolicyShipping PolicySecurity PolicyCookie PolicyTerms and ConditionsDigital Downloads (PDF)
$0.00
Basket
Search
ClosePrivacy PolicyTecla Editions is committed to keeping the personal details of its visitors and customers private and secure (information is collected and stored in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998).We will not sell or share your personal details with anyone else.The type of information we will collect about you includes:your nameaddressemail addressWe use the personal information you give us for the following purposes:to contact you about the status of your order.to efficiently process and dispatch your order to your delivery address.to change and enhance the web site.to occasionally email you with details of our products, special promotions, and enhancements. If you would prefer not to receive these mailings, you can unsubscribe from our mailing list by clicking the Unsubscribe link included at the bottom of every newsletter.to conduct anonymous and aggregate research into a) the way our web site is used and b) the purchasing patterns of our customers.PayPal TransactionsIn addition to the Privacy Policy outlined above, all PayPal transactions placed on the Tecla Editions website are also subject to the PayPal Privacy Policy.Cookie PolicyWe may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This can include using a “cookie” which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings.The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our Security Policy and the law.If you have any questions about Tecla Editions’s Privacy Policy please email them to info@tecla.com.Mauro Giuliani – New Tecla 2020 re-engraved editions of his works for flute or violin and guitarThe new 2020 digital edition of Sor’s New Complete Works for GuitarFernando Sor – the 27 FREE TO EVERYBODY filesJosep Maria Mangado’s La Guitarra en Cataluña
and his new book about the PalauWhy the Tecla edition of Beethoven’s 32 piano sonatas is the only way to goShipping Dates (and Brexit)Doing what I (and Tecla) can for the planetWhat you need to know about copyrightTecla NewsAssociated Board (ABRSM)Music for voice and guitar
MenuMauro Giuliani – New Tecla 2020 re-engraved editions of his works for flute or violin and guitarThe new 2020 digital edition of Sor’s New Complete Works for GuitarFernando Sor – the 27 FREE TO EVERYBODY filesJosep Maria Mangado’s La Guitarra en Cataluña
and his new book about the PalauWhy the Tecla edition of Beethoven’s 32 piano sonatas is the only way to goShipping Dates (and Brexit)Doing what I (and Tecla) can for the planetWhat you need to know about copyrightTecla NewsAssociated Board (ABRSM)Music for voice and guitarTecla Editions
Sendinblue Newsletter
If you would like to be informed about new Tecla publications, please sign up here. Email Address*
Remember Me
Log In
Lost your password?
|
Register
This site uses cookies: Find out more.Ok
